# PRIYANKA

# **THOSAR**

SR. WEB / GRAPHIC DESIGNER

# EDUCATION

Digital Marketing Course Diploma in Advanced Computer Arts (DACA) B.Com.

Internet Swaggers Digital Marketing Institute (2019) Mumbai Education Trust (Under C-DAC) (2006-07) KTHM College, Nashik, Pune University (2006)

# EXPERIENCE

# **TOTAL 10+ YEARS**

## Acme IT Solutions, Nashik

#### December 2021 - Current

Working as a Senior Web & Graphic Designer including Adobe Photoshop, HTML5/CSS3, Bootstrap3/Less, WordPress, CorelDraw, Adobe Illustrator. Projects below:

SMM posts design | regaloil.in | FabFinance Web & Mobile App | Online Mall Africa Web & Mobile App | some ongoing projects.

# Freelancing

#### March 2018 - December 2021

Worked as a Freelancer - Web & Graphic Designer including Adobe Photoshop, HTML5/CSS3, Bootstrap3/Less, WordPress, CorelDraw, Adobe Illustrator. Projects below:

kwantumchemicals.com | uniqueaquasystems.com | sssps.in | envichem.in

#### adroitCoders, Nashik

#### March 2010 - March 2018

Worked as a Senior Web & Graphic Designer including Adobe Photoshop, HTML5/CSS3, Bootstrap3/Less, WordPress, CorelDraw, Adobe Illustrator. Projects below:

golidays.net | scrissorboy.com | Wella, Kadus, Beauty Force: Android and iOS apps | Wella, Nixion, Clairol: Interactive books | pravartakpathak.com | klasseweasche.com | prima.co.at | thallercenter.at | starsnbars.com | mehrperspektiven.de | ClearKarma web & iOS app

# Repro India Ltd., Navi Mumbai

#### November 2007 - February 2010

Worked as a Graphic Designer including Adobe Photoshop, CorelDraw, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe InDesign, Adobe Flash. Projects below: Franchising Focus Magazine design | Designed kids books, e-books, brouchers, diary | IIITB, Aptech books cover design

#### Web Animation Studio, Mumbai

#### February 2007 - October 2007

Worked as a Junior Flash & Graphic Designer including Adobe Photoshop, CorelDraw, Adobe Flash. Projects below:

Kich CD presentation | Mobile2Win CD presentation | iDent CD presentation | Designed Brochures for ABN Amro

## CONTACT INFO

PHONE

+91 9975701138

 $\bowtie$ 

**EMAIL** 

priyankarthosar@gmail.com

2

**ADDRESS** 

Flat No. 22, Anadvan, Tarwala Nagar, Dindori Road, Nashik - 422004. Maharashtra, India.

# **ABOUT ME**

I am a web & graphic designer, having a good knowledge & experience of web & print media. I find great interest in all new digital technologies and latest design practices. I would like to bring design ideas live. I have passion for creating beautiful, intuitive responsive websites for project that work on.

# EXPERTISE

#### Softwares

Adobe Photoshop

- Adobe Dreamweaver

- CorelDraw

Adobe Illustrator

- Adobe Flash

- Adobe Premiere

## Languages & Skills

- HTML5/CSS3

- WordPress

- Bootstrap3/LESS/SASS

- SEO, Keyword Reseach

- Social Media Marketing

# \*\*\*\*

食食食食食

\*\*\*

\*\*\*\*

会会会会会

\*\*\*

\*\*\*\*

\*\*\*\*\*

# ACHIEVEMENTS

Key Employee 2013: Rewarded by "Key employee of adroitCoders".

Divya Marathi Fotomania: 2nd prize in "Nature" category photography.

#### HOBBIES

Photography, Travelling, Reading, Singing, Drawing

#### PERSONAL INFO

Date of Birth: Languages: Marital Status: 3 January 1986 Marathi, Hindi, English

Married